Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
Then, thus, a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting.
Either way, I'm feeling alive.
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Here we go.
Raise your flag up high.
Hail a brand new dawn.
Blaze across the sky.
Time to journey on.
On your mark.
Come above the king.
We're on Earth, a legendary. Hooray.
If you can show your breath?
Then we'll make some waves.
We run our daunted!
Ain't no beginners.
Cause if you're wanted!
Then you're a winner.
For we are on the cruise.
And freedom is the only rule.
Fearless night and day!
Cause that's just our way.
Find one piece.
I'll be the first.
I'll put it be so bad!
I could burst.
It's all this real.
It must be cause my hand's on the wheel.
I'm done playing, filled with the waiting.
In a world I'm feeling
alive, but I'll be loud.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far.
Gotta make it to the end!
Whatever danger we find,
no one ever left behind.
I've always got your back, my friend.
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward.
Dreaming from the very
first day, I'd make my name.
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed.
I'm done playing through,
it's a wave in the air.
The world I'm feeling
alive, look out below.
Wake up, sunshine.
Wake up, sunshine here?
We go!
Looks like it's about to blow!
Pull back, men!
We'll live to plunder
another day! Yeah, roger!
You don't gotta ask me twice!
Antelope, Baratsumi, draw the ship!
Okay, Captain, sure!
And the second is my name, and these
long-lost bridges out it later!
Oh, no!
Luffy, I don't know how the Kraken works,
but order him to turn around and haul ass!
Hey, Sodomy!
Wait a sec!
He's hauling ass just fine all on his own!
We're such a giant monster,
it's kind of shameful, actually!
Who cares?
I would be doing the same thing.
He runs terribly.
Give him a break.
I'd rather be clumsy and alive
than graceful and dead. Come on.
I want to see lava.
Evacuate to the front of the ship. Harry!
That's not going to help.
It's just a couple of feet.
Well, you've got your lava, Luffy.
It's getting hotter.
Nobody told me we could
be boiled alive down here.
The ocean sure hates us.
Is this a fly?
Is this a good or bad?
Faster You can do it.
The temperature change.
It's causing a vortex in the current.
Nami?
Which direction is Fishman Island?
We can't lose our way.
You're not ready for real world yet.
Straight ahead.
I have an idea.
We're getting closer.
Now jump into the trench.
That's not a place you jump!
It's an abyss!
No!
There's something to blackness down there!
Fish people live there!
It's gotta be insane!
Lava!
There's lava behind us!
And the void in front of us! Help!
Can't we go up? Up?
Where's that burning and dark
and everything wants to kill us?
Wait, you're being really gloomy, are you?
You're some evil demon who looks like him
and wants to drag us
to the depths of hell!
This is a nightmare!
Why can't I wake up?
Zootaman!
Jump in!
It's erupting again!
Look above us!
Something's coming down!
Baldur's?
A mudslide?
It's an avalanche! Brace yourself!
The eruption knocked the rocks loose!
If one of those hits us,
then the sun is done for!
Judge the Baldur's, so do me!
I can't just sit here.
I'm going to go cut them.
Luffy, hold onto my leg, okay?
Sure, gotcha!
Zara, you can't!
What's the big idea?
Yeah, let him go, Robin!
The ship is over 8,000
meters deep right now!
Never mind the boulders!
Go outside or the water
pressure will crush you!
Fine, but we gotta do something!
Special Attack Green Star Sargasso!
Usa made seaweed appear!
It stopped the boulders!
That's handy!
Oh, wow! Nice shot!
It won't hold for very long, though.
We gotta get moving, Tsurume! Move it!
Just in time!
Monster plants? Oh, man! That's cool!
I wonder what else you have
in that big bag of tricks.
Looks like we're in the clear!
You were pretty great
too, Sudamane! Sudamane!
Sudamane!
Aren't we alive or dead?
There's light, but we're
so deep in the sea.
So bright!
I've got stars in my eyes.
Rather, just stars, they're in the eyes.
Guys, check it out over there.
I think we made it.
I can't see anything, it's too bright!
Come on, Nami, tell us!
Yep, there's no doubt about it!
The needle is pointing straight ahead!
We did it!
Fishman Island!
It's huge!
It's in a giant bubble!
It looks like they have clouds!
All right, we made it!
The New World is next!
Almost there!
Well, what do you know?
The moron survived!
After all, this is
where the mermaids live!
Real life!
Beautiful mermaids!
My dream can finally come true!
How I've longed to see their faces!
To touch them!
Hold up!
You're not ready for this!
You shouldn't even think about it!
Doctor!
I'm sorry.
I thought my treatment would do the trick.
I know it's your dream, but you're
not healthy enough for mermaids.
Doctor!
For him, this is a fate worse than death.
There's got to be something you can do!
If he sees mermaids, it will be death!
How cruel!
I don't care.
Saji!
I don't want to live in
a world without dreams.
I'd rather die there and
get some hot mermaid tail.
You're the worst!
Who needs blood?
I have lust to sustain me! Whoa!
It's let your rebirth bright!
I'm so hungry.
I bet they fry up all kinds of
yummy deep-sea monsters down here.
Hey, wipe up that drool
and tell City Mae to go.
There's an entrance around here
somewhere, and we've got to find it.
Guys, we got company!
Oh, crap. That's not good.
No bones!
And now we're dead!
Wow, they look tough!
I want one!
Why would you allow these foolish
humors to tell you what to do? Crack in.
What the heck, Tsutamae?
Seriously, we were almost there!
You guys are the straw
hat pirates aren't you?
You have quite the
reputation for starters.
You were the ones who ruined
the Arlong pirate's plans.
That part makes sense at least.
But for some reason two
years back when Hachi
was in trouble you stood
up for your old enemy.
And then you clocked one of the
celestial dragons right in his ugly face.
Fisher tiger happened to
do the exact same thing,
and he's the hero of this entire island.
Fisher tiger?
I'm not sure what to do with you.
Tell it to me straight.
Are you supposed to be our enemies or not?
How about I give you an
option enlist under our
banner as members of
the new fishman pirates?
Or else or else meaning
we sink you right now!
What you say fuel up Franky hurry huh?
You got a plan?
You and I both know that luffy isn't
going to cooperate with these guys!
But we're 10 000 meters underwater
right now and if we try to fight them
we don't stand a chance of winning
especially not with those sea monsters!
So we have to go!
I need you to use all of the
oxygen we have to make a giant
Kaido burst so we can charge
straight into fishman island!
Whoa you kidding me?
We've come way too far to die here!
I agree it's risky but it's likely
our only chance at surviving this!
If that's the case I'm gonna
fill it up right away! Franky!
Steer the ship!
Everything's gonna be just super!
So, have you decided if you want to
be part of our crew, Straw Hat Luffy?
Yeah, right, you wish! Stupid!
Are you sure about that?
You did hear me say what will
happen if you refuse, didn't you?
Guess you are the enemy of the fishmen.
Nothing but filthy human scum
that's
a real shame you won't be seeing
Fish Man Island after all see Lion
all right filled up and ready to move
Don't forget, we got our own life!
Maybe we can fight some
other time, alright?
Here goes...
To the burn!
Look at him go!
Can't breathe!
There's no more air!
I'm getting squeezed!
Hang on!
We'll make it no matter what!
What in the hell?
What's up with that crazy ship?
We're on our way in!
I'll be with you soon, beautiful mermaid!
We lost the coning!
It got stuck when we crossed the bubble!
This bubble, it's a double structure.
A normal ship would crash
because there's nothing but air.
We're about to run into another bubble.
You guys ready?
Water?
This current is really strong.
Help me!
I can't breathe!
Crap!
Four of us can't swim!
Come on!
Freeze!
Nani! Bravo!
Dammit!
I can't resist the current!
That's one way to get in.
Pretty reckless, though.
Well, we could still go in after
them if you want to, Hammond.
No way to know if they're
alive or dead, though.
Yeah, let's track them down.
We can't let Neptune's army get their
hands on them first, now can we?
But before we do anything, we should go
back to Noah and tell the boss what's up.
I think he'd want to know that the
man who ruined Arlong's plan is here.
Hey!
Take a look.
I'll look.
I won't.
Maybe I'll look.
Who cares if I look?
Now he's moving.
He moved.
No, he didn't.
He might have moved.
Who cares if he moved?
Alright, he's alive.
Thank goodness.
Where am I?
Oh, Luffy-chin
It's been a while, hasn't it?
So how are you feeling?
Hey, it's Kuma.
It's nice to see you!
Oh, Kuma, you've got so lovely?
Kuma
Wait a minute, if Kami's here, we
made it to Fishman Island after all?
Yeah, we did!
From what I understand,
we were about to drown, but then we
were rescued by a bunch of mermaids!
That's right!
Sanji Chopper and I just
woke up a few minutes ago.
Guess we're pretty lucky, huh?
Lucky enough to wake up in Kami's house.
Here, catch. Uh-oh!
So this is your house?
My bad!
I know I was supposed to
pick you guys up on Sabo Odi,
but I was thinking that
was another month from now.
That's okay.
Where is everybody?
Well, uh, it looks like we got separated.
Goodness, I hope they're safe.
So they're lost?
Well, I'm sure it'll turn out okay, right?
They're fine.
The Bonehead can't do much underwater.
But the Robot and Mosshead are probably
with them, so I wouldn't worry. Right.
Everything will be just fine.
I hope I get to see them again soon.
Anyway, here you go.
I'm sure you're all freezing, so I made
some soup that'll warm you right up.
Daddy!
Cold seaweed soup! It's yummy!
It's cold?
That's not right!
How are you supposed to get
bored if the soup is cold?
I'm sorry!
I'm such a failure!
The soup is great, Kuma.
I'm warmer already.
That doesn't make sense.
Come on, let me try some too!
Your clothes are dry, everybody.
They're dry.
No, they're not dry.
Your clothes might be dry.
Who cares if they're dry?
You keep care of our clothes too?
Well, thanks
Who are those little guys?
Oh, there's some friends of mine.
The Medica Mermaid Quintuplets.
I'm Ichka, I'm Nika, I'm Sanka,
I'm Young, and I'm Young too.
Wait, why are there two Yonkas?
They're really fast swimmers
and pretty clever as well.
Yeah?
Nice to meet you.
I've got a lot of neat
friends here, actually.
This is the seafloor of the Mermaid Cove,
home to the girls' dorm of
the famous Mermaid Cafe.
Huh?
The girls' dorm?
Oh, it's just this cute little
cafe where I work as a waitress.
We have a lot of pretty
mermaids there on staff.
Sachi!
Don't die!
I won't die! No, no!
I swore I made a promise to myself that
for the entire time I
was on Fishman Island,
I wouldn't get a nosebleed and pass out.
And I've held out for this long,
so I deserve a reward, right?
Pathetic.
I know.
Why don't we go up there now?
I'll introduce you to all of my friends.
Whoa, a turtle!
Sea turtle elevator, huh?
Could you give us a lift, Mr.
Turtle?
This is a coral apartment complex.
The dorms are at the very
bottom, so rent's cheap.
The top floor is the most expensive
because it gets natural light.
Hmm.
Does that mean you're poor?
And what about Hachi and Papagu?
Hatchan got beat up real
bad about a year ago.
Oh, yeah, I heard about that.
He was protecting the sunny
forest back on Sabaori, right?
Hatchan came from the Fishman District,
so that's where he's been
resting and recovering.
I haven't had the chance
to see him lately,
but from what I hear, he's
getting better all the time.
Huh? He's okay?
Yeah, but it's kind of
a rough part of town.
If you guys go along with me,
I wouldn't mind heading over
there to visit him, though.
Let's do it!
I've been wanting to
thank him face to face!
Sure, you got it.
And, well, as for Papa Goo, he's
a super famous fashion designer.
So he lives in a big, fancy mansion in the
high-class district of Fishfrily Hills.
I'm supposed to deliver
some clams over there today.
You want to come with me?
Wait, he's your pet, but you two
don't live in the same place?
Yeah, cause that area is a
little out of my price range.
We have better clams here anyway!
Huh?
Hey, what's that drinking
straw looking tube, Dial?
Oh, that thing?
That's the water road, the
bubble craftsman built it.
And when mermaids or fish
get inside it, well, hold on!
Here, let me show you.
It's the surface!
We made it! Luigi!
Look!
I'm swimming in the sky!
Wait a sec!
If we're underwater, why do
we see a sky full of clouds?
Hey, Kuma! Huh?
It's a girl!
Where's that coming from?
Hey, guys!
Are these your pirate friends?
I guess that means they
didn't drown after all.
You didn't come in through the
entrance like you're supposed to,
so we were concerned.
Well, hi there.
You're not as scary as I thought you'd be.
So you broke in?
That's pretty hot.
I kind of have a thing for pirates.
It's like a real-life fairy tale!
A coral paradise!
A whole cone full of mermaids!
What's the matter with Soji now?
He didn't even cry this hard
when he left the Breath egg.
Finally!
I found my all-blue after all these years!
Are you sure about that? Really?
Here, let me introduce everybody.
That's Luffy-chin, he's the captain.
Yeah, nice to meet you.
Sachi-Chin's the crybaby.
The nose guy is Usopp-Chin.
That's me.
And the raccoon is Chopper-Chin.
Not again!
Why are you crying?
Come over here.
Let's dance in the water together.
Okay, I get it.
This is obviously too good to be true.
Maybe I'm destined to die today.
That's dark!
What the heck happened to you in the
last two years to make you this gloomy?
Isn't this supposed to be
the land of your dreams?
You crack me up, Sanji.
I don't think he's joking!
Hey,
that barrel over there is the one that
drifted in with all Kamey's friends, right?
What's in it?
Maybe treasure?
Uh, I don't know.
It's sealed pretty tightly,
so it's got to be important.
Yeah?
I think we should open it.
Interesting.
So Straw Hat finally made
it to our turf, did he?
Good for him.
Right.
What are we going to do about it, boss?
I want you to bring him here.
And quickly.